I'm Carter Gold.
I'm Bobby Gold.
I'm Czech Gold.
If you want to know what
it's like to walk a day in our shoes,
this isn't a fairy tale. This is our
real lives.
I don't give a [ __ ]
We are the Golden Brothers.
Today is Bobby Gold's son's birthday party,
but with a major deal looming in
the background,
the Golden Brothers are
feeling some tension.
The duplex is already in escrow.
[ __ ] you, you [ __ ] piece of [ __ ]
Hi, I'm Fronnie.
Nice to meet y'all.
Yes. So, I'm Bobby's girl.
Bobb's the businessman.
Well, there wasn't water in the basement
when I sold it.
[ __ ] you.
Oh, he got a temper.
No, I don't want fries, you [ __ ]
piece of [ __ ]
What do you mean the car washes closed,
Jagoff?
And Carter, he's a dramatic one.
I'm going to kill myself.
No, you're not. Stop. No, you're not. Stop. Stop.
I'm going to faint.
You're not going to faint. You're not going to
stop. Stop. You're not going to faint.
Now, check.
You know what? I'm pretty sure he's
blind.
just put that there.
No, no, that's that that's been there.
- What' you say?
- It's been there.
You know, he's always acting like he's
tired.
Yeah, i'm tired.
He's just tired.
It's always been there.
If he's tired, he's tired. [ __ ] you.
Calm down.
Okay. So, what's everybody wearing?
I'm going to be wearing this gold chain.
unfucking real.
If it's your special day, you wear the gold chain.
Every gold brother knows that.
My brother is just being a jackass.
And if there's one thing that I
hate, it's guys being jackasses.
This is my day. This is my son's birthday.
I'm
the only one that gets to wear the gold
chain.
Who the [ __ ] made you the gold chain police?
I'm
so sorry.
I know it's little baby Benjamin's birthday,
but I'll be [ __ ] if I'm not
wearing that chain.
What the [ __ ] Carter?
Hi. Uh, I'm a school psychologist.
I need to talk to somebody about Charlie.
I think he's unwell.
There's a fourth brother, but you ain't
know that.
It's a fourth brother.
He's a little weird named Charlie.
Hi, my name's Charlie and I hate this show.
Sometimes it just feels like no
one's listening to me.
Charlie is insufferable.
I don't like listening to him.
I don't like looking like I'm
listening to him.
- Are you his girlfriend?
- No.
That would be that would be cool.
- I'm a psychologist.
- Oh, read his palm.
Can you Can you Thank you so much.
Check on Charlie. Come check on Charlie.
- We'll give him a look.
I'm the only one that gets to wear the
gold chain.
If you guys keep treating me like this,
I'm going to end up [ __ ] blowing my own head off.
You guys want me to blow
off my [ __ ] head?
Is that what you want?
You want me to blow off my own
head?
- No.
You know, I'll cut my own [ __ ] head off.
I'm wearing the gold chain or we're
not coming.
- That'll come.
- Fine.
Oh, and for your information.
Fine. That's fine.
Look, when there's a problem, we call daddy.
And when daddy comes to town,
I'm the daddy. I'm the duplex king.
You live in the area. Of course, you've seen
my signs.
You know my sons.
And if you've bought a duplex in the last 5
years, you've bought it from me.
Or made
a terrible mistake.
Daddy came over, but the caterers were
in the kitchen,
so we had to meet in
Charlie's room.
But oh boy,
you need to take that off.
Daddy, it's my special day. Tell him to lose it.
What the [ __ ] Let him wear the chain.
Daddy, I hear you. But I got to tell
you, if I take this chain off before the party,
I'm gonna [ __ ] kill myself.
Shut the [ __ ] up, you fat [ __ ] toilet ogre.
You'll not do [ __ ]
If they make me take this chain off,
I'm going to kill my [ __ ] wife and then
hang myself in the garage.
What are you guys doing in my space?
Charlie, this room's a [ __ ] mess.
Don't say sorry, just [ __ ] clean it.
I'm sorry.
Don't you talk to him like that.
Charlie, how are you, buddy?
It's like
it's like pretty cool.
school is good and
it's just like sometimes everyone's
like, you know, you're not like your brothers.
Like when your your brothers
were here, you know, they'd like raise hell
and like do all kinds of like crazy [ __ ]
shut
- Charlie, let me stop you there for a
second.
- Yeah.
Anybody ever tell you you're a real
tough hang? Anybody tell you that?
You want to come back here with all this
[ __ ] crybaby [ __ ]
when we're back
here talking about making money?
What are you, a [ __ ] dumbass?
Instead
of selling duplexes, you're back here
cutting the heads off of bears
like some
type of [ __ ] gay [ __ ]
I mean, I can see [ __ ] them, but
cutting their heads off?
Listen to what I have to say.
Listen to what I have to say to you.
Every litter of horses has a run.
And guess what?
You're right.
Now, if you don't mind,
the stallion's got to romp around a
little bit back here.
Let's get the [ __ ]
out of here.
Okay. Thank you, Charlie.
I mean, what the [ __ ] Jesus.
All right, enough of this. How about you
both wear a gold chain?
- Exactly.
- All right, D. I'm going to wear
a gold chain, too, then.
Well, if you're going to wear one, then
- Yeah, I'm definitely going to wear one.
- Yeah, we're all wearing one.
No. No.
Take that off or get the [ __ ] out of
fine. I'm leaving then.
If this chain comes off, I'm going to
blow my head off in front of all the
kids at the party.
This is getting out of control.
Come on, man. We got a birthday party to get
ready for.
Excuse
me, sir. I really need to talk to you
about your son, Charlie.
He's at a
extremely delicate age with his mental health
and he's been saying some things
at school that
Are you talking to me?
The birthday party's in full swing,
but Bobby and Carter's feud could
potentially drive the family
and
business apart.
[ __ ] [ __ ] you.
Things got out of control and I told
Bobby, "You got to text Carter. Come on, man.
This is getting out of control. I
need to do a voiceto text message to Carter.
Hey Carter, sorry I was being a
bad [ __ ] earlier,
but
what are you up to?
I was mad at Bobby,
but then he started
acting like a real [ __ ] in the text chain.
Now I just kind of feel bad for
him.
[ __ ] you, but also I'm sorry.
It is your big day. I'm sorry.
Thank you.
I hate drama.
Turns out everything did work out.
I guess you could say in the end that
everything turned out
pretty much my my best friend. And on
the day of judgment,
golden.